Yuna Mogiha is a channel
Today, April 2, is the day of my Nana Okada's graduation performance
Yurimogi is a little different
Today I would like to take a behind-the-scenes shot of it!
You mean the last theater performance?
Yes, the last theater performance.
That's great.
The sun is setting.
Is this your last performance?
That's right. So the next time I see you guys...
I'll be Nana Okada, the non-AKB Nana.
Just Nana.
I'm just Nana without a name.
I was at a concert yesterday.
It ended at 10:00 p.m.
It was over at 10, but I got home at midnight.
I went to bed at 4:00.
When I woke up, it was 7:00. I was like...
I didn't sleep.
I couldn't sleep.
I'm sleepy, but I'll try.
I'll try my best.
Extra
I noticed your picture.
What? No way.
I didn't notice.
Oh, no, On-chan.
What?
If you didn't have your lip glass yesterday, you wouldn't have noticed.
Isn't that bad?
Ugo, I'm at the front of the line, so I didn't notice.
Yeah.
I saw your picture.
Yeah, that's how I found out about you.
What?
I have a new name.
I'm far away, so I didn't know about you.
I didn't recognize you. You're early.
It's been a long time since I've had a Reproducer's Day.
You just...
You cried a little, didn't you? Did you laugh? You were laughing!
Crying and laughing.
I've been crying since the "poochie" part... the crying part.
I was crying and smiling, and we were both playing with toys.
I cried so hard at most of the memories too!
I also cried a lot at the Philosophy Love retreat.
Really?
Nata Asha cried a lot yesterday.
Oh, I know! Nataasha was so good!
Nataasha made you cry?
Nataasha is amazing! I was crying the whole rehearsal.
I was crying. It was so good.
I'm so happy.
Can we see the graduation concert on
Can I watch the graduation concert on Nana Okada's New Year's Eve channel?
Yes! You can see the whole backstage, so this time it's the backstage of the concert.
Yes, you can watch it, too!
Nice to meet you!
I will never forget the flowers you gave me that day
The language of rainbow-colored flowers is infinite possibilities
I'm tone deaf, actually.
Oh, no! Do you want to take it apart?
Yes, yes, yes, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
The last one.
I want to stay close to the memories that will become small.
I got the upper half tone.
I'm still a little out of tune.
It's impossible. Yes, but I had them send me a sound file of just the hamoris.
I practiced at home.
It's not good at all.
It's fine.
But rhythm is easier.
Is that so? Then I'll work on it so we can harmonize some day.
I'm glad.
He can't sing the main melody backwards.
That's great. That's really great.
The main melody is like this.
Take off the red nail polish you put on in the morning.I dropped the red nail polish I had done in the morning.
I got it from Nana-chan.
She's cute.
Are you wearing green, too?
I think green is better for you, too, Nana-chan.
Green.
Yui's color.
The mask is green.
Milo.
Oh, no.
When I put it on, green is flowing from somewhere.
When I tie it on, it's all green.
It's amazing.
Good morning.
Thank you very much for all your preparation for my graduation performance today.
New Answer's Tomaman, please give my best regards.
Pleased to meet you.
Is someone lying?
I know, but it still bothers me.
Because I like you.
But back then...
Good night.
What do you want me to tell him? What do you want me to tell him?
I'm thinking about what's right in front of my eyes
I'm looking at you through my chest
Because this is the place
I'm wiping my cheeks and spilling tears
live deep in my heart
now ζел objections
Don't let the road go by
Even if life disappears
I have no regrets
I don't want to hold on to your name
I don't want to hold on to it
I'll stay soaking wet
All the trees of today
I'm not holding on to it
A good story
Standing in each other's fashion
Tourists at the foot of the seat
in the wagon mens cans
you did the elevator
From the beginning
Even when you least expect it
The end
Halfway around the world
It was your face that I hated
The flowers you gave me that day
I'll never forget the rainbow-colored flowers
Words are infinite possibilities
Mommy is a Baby
Thanks for watching!
I drew a card.
You can do it.
I can do it.
You can do it!
Dreams are in the sweat
A flower blooming little by little
Hold them together, just like that
I can't betray you
Gently holding hands
You remember me so well
I've just learned until now
where the uniform is the same
Beyond the smaller
That's when I jumped up
Go! Wake!
I'm Elgie the cat.
I haven't been able to tell you this for a long time.
I haven't told you this in a long time.
You have a beautiful cat.
You know, it's always better than you think.
It's good to want each other
Falling in love all the time
And make the sadness go away
Yoo-chan made this for me.
Not even close.
Yoo-chan made 90.90
Yes, it's different.Yes, sir. No, sir.
9.99
Eh, cute!
Nachan is so cute!
Cute, cute
Team.
Oh, nice, nice.
Oh, what's this?
Why are you here?
And here we go
Oh, my God.
You wrote all this for me.
Here, that's right, all of them.
All of them are Yoo-chan's handwriting.
Around here
Oh, that area.
I did the collage here.
Lovely
At the end
Nae-chan's joining in.
I'll put this in and then we're done.
Then the last
A stroke of the pen
Oh!
It's done.
Finished.
That's great.
Next song
Have a good day!
Nana Okada's graduation lecture
The show will start without a pause
Oh!
Maybe a little closer at the end.
Like a little more back to back.
Oh, yeah, right, right. Tell them we'll love each other.
When I say, "The song is over," move away.
Okada-san, the graduation show is about to start.
Yes, cute.
Have you grown taller again?
I've grown taller.
I knew it.
You don't look like a ninth grader.
Nice to meet you.
The guy in the back is a jerk.
I love you.
Do it.
What are you going to do?
You're so cute, Momochan!
Something's here.
You're so cute.
It's flying... it's flying... one more time...
I was looking at the rainbow ink and I felt like crying
Why so cute!
Don't cry, Tamo-chan!
Tamochan doesn't cry
I can't see this guy on the left
I'm looking forward to it too
You're so sweet.
What's this?
It's with Renzel.
What is it? I'm so happy.
What's this?
It's some kind of fire.
It's a fire.
Look at it.
The fire heals you, doesn't it?
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
I love it.
I'm going to put some forest ball eyeliner in the back.
I'm serious.
Stop it!
Bad boy!
What are you going to put on?
I'm going to put lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lameI'm thinking of putting lame lame lame.
I don't know what color to use.
I don't know what color to get.
Yesterday I went with silver and red.
I want to change it from yesterday.
I've done it around...
I'm not sure if I want to go with my favorite color.
I'm not sure if I'm going to go with green.
Or maybe I'll go with a spring pink.
Or maybe cherry blossoms?
That's right.
So cute!
It's so cute!
The bracelet is all red.
But it's very Nana-chan.
Really?
I think I'll get the pink and green.
Let's mix them both.
Let's mix them.
Nice!
It's done!
So cute!
It's so cute!
It looks good!
This is how we're going to do it.
I'm going to take on the challenge with this.
I think it's good.
A little bit.
The color of the mascara is different.
The rhinestones are a different color.
The lip color is a little bit different.
Various colors to match the outfits.
Cute! Strong!
Isn't it almost half an hour?
Once it starts, it'll be over in two hours.
Okay, Nae-chan.
You mean you only have two hours left in your AKB life?
That's not good.
I can't believe it.
I can't really feel it right now.
I usually don't have that much time.
We don't reject radishes too much, do we?
I almost cried a little yesterday.
But I don't think I'll cry today.
I don't think I'll cry today.
You don't really feel it, do you?
That's true.
When someone graduates...
People who come to you...
I'm not feeling it right now.
But you don't feel it either.
She says she doesn't feel it until about two weeks after she stops going to lessons.
I think I'll finally feel it after about two weeks.
Maybe that's what Tom said.
That's what Tom said.
Since she stopped going to work and lessons...
Finally, I realized that I'm not an AKB.
It will take 2 more weeks from here, Aachan
I think she'll finally start crying in two weeks.
Why are you embarrassed?
What?
Aren't the three of us taking pictures?
Aren't we taking pictures?
Please.
Is it red? Are you okay? Red.
Can we not have a pink background?
Pink background, please.
I'll go work on it.
Oh, Mr. Moguy.
Wow, that's nice.
Engine, please.
It's not a character.
I'll get the engine.
Nana Okada, we're going to the graduation show.
Ooh!
Congratulations!
How do you feel, Yoo-chan?
I really don't feel it.
I understand.
I'm going to miss you.
I'll miss you.I miss you.
What's with the face?
They're staring at me.
What?
The Okada Alliance.
I miss him.
Girl power.
She's cute.
Girl power?
What? A letter?
Cute.
That's nice.
It's the forbidden couple.
Oh, my God.
Too much fun, right?
A 14-year-old and an 18-year-old.
I don't know if I'm allowed to do this with a 14-year-old.
I was thinking...
The producer said something about freedom of expression.
Freedom of expression.
I think it's a new frontier.
It's a new frontier, isn't it?
Okay, have a good day.
Oh, my God!
Have a good day.
Oh, no!
Yuuchan!
Come on, it's going to be scary!
I bought clothes for everyone!
The guests applauded!
How's your mouth?
You're all washed up!
Applause from the audience
Thank you very much for coming to today's AKB48 Nana Okada graduation performance.
Due to the circumstances of today's performance, the emergency line in the auditorium will be raised and lowered.
Please check the entrance and exit in advance.
Next, we have Idol Last Day.
I think it's a coincidence,
Isn't it 300 days?
It is 3,977 days today.
So we can make it 3,977 days.
It's too much to be a coincidence, isn't it?
Wait a minute, I'm not supposed to drink tapioca.
Leaving soon? Wait a little longer.
That's all for now.
Yunamogi.
Tomorrow.
Latte update.
It's not good. That's right.
My taste in music has begun.
Like you don't need to see it.
I was just putting on an act.
A little more square back.
How many times do you think I've told you?
There's a director.
You've got to make a final decision here,
And then we'll switch it up.
And then the graduation show will begin.
That's important, but that's it.
It's important, but that's it.
This is the last time we can leave something like this to our juniors.
I want to tell them something for sure for the last time.
I want to tell them something.
The afterglow is very important.
Akarara's graduation performance is about to begin!
I've never thought about it.
What is this?
Is it wrong?
I'm stuck.
Mike's good.
Okay, here we go. Here we go.
Have fun.
I'll go with you.
It's the light blue group.
Good luck, light blue group!
Oh, they look like this.
I wanted to put these on all at once, but they're putting them on like this.
It's going to be a big problem at the end.
They are so cute.
There's the light blue group again.
Have a nice trip.Have a good day.
I'm off.
I'm changing into my dress.
Wow, four people are working on you right now.
Luxurious, isn't it?
It's amazing.
My goal is to sing without crying.
My goal is to sing without crying, and to deliver the lyrics well.
That's great.
Wow, it looks heavy.
It weighs 6 kilograms. Wow. A 6 kg skirt.
The hair ornament is beautiful, too. The hair ornaments, too, one by one, carefully.
You see this fine one here? These are all individually attached. Beads.
By the costume designer. Aren't they beautiful?
Oh, the earrings are handmade, too. You didn't buy these earrings, did you? Wait a minute. Wait a minute, sis.
Oh, my goodness, they're beautiful.
How beautiful? About this pretty.
You're beautiful.
You look good.
I'm in the way.
You're beautiful.
Photographers!
Have a good day.
I'm going to go sing my way to adulthood.
I'm going to cry.
No, I'm going to cry if I hear "The Road to Adulthood.
There's something in there.
Paint.
Okay.
Have a good day.
The back is absolutely fine.
The center is great.
Is it good?
Very good.
I got it.
Here you go.
Sacred verse, line and hat.
Jidan: Gege also left pillow
Melody. Kama finger arrow.
When you smile. It's cuimeji.
If something hot flows
I try to live my life looking forward
The long and regrettable road to adulthood
No matter what time it is
Fang climbing
Everyone is reborn
Let's wipe away our tears and start walking
The road to adulthood that you can see there
Subtitle & Subtitle Kyou
The 14th term members are crying because they're not wearing their costumes.
It's like they're graduating.
I know, I know!
This is Yunamogio channel!
I'm Yumogio channel. Pleased to meet you.
I'm sorry.
I'm a senior in the 14th term.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I feel like the era we've been watching is coming to an end.
I can feel it.
Graduation is a slope.
The pledge of the tournament
Soon I'll be smiling too much for love
I want to be with you forever, my love
See you again in 10 years
Well, that's it, Na-chan, the graduation show is over!
Congratulations!
Yay!
Thank you!
My impressions can be summed up in one word,
This is such an important first week of the graduation performance,
I am happy to leave such an important first week of graduation performances on the Yuna-Mogiwan Channel!
Nice one word!
That's all.
So, I hope you will continue to support YunaMogiwan Channel and AKB48,
And I hope you will continue to support AKB48,
Good button and please subscribe to our channel!
Please also support me as one Nana Okada!Please support me as one Nana Okada!
Bye bye!
Please continue to support Yuna Mogiwan forever!
Yoo-hoo!
Now that the performance is over
I'd like to take off the company.
The day has finally come.
Eee...
Once I'm out of the office, I'm really done.
It won't take long.
No, it won't.
But someday you'll realize it.
Ugh.
All kinds of people are watching behind me.
I'll miss you... Oh, there you are, there you are.
Thank you very much. Thank you for the title.
There you go.
Supper.
Supper. Okay.
Okay.
Here we go.
It's off.
So, thank you all for your support over the past 10 years.
It's been a really fun 10 years.
A lot has happened, but I will always love AKB48.
Yay! Is everyone taking this kabisha home with them?
Oh! They are nodding. Then let's take it home. It's going to be like home. Let's try not to die.
Thank you for your hard work! Let's make this an extra video.
We can really make it look like Barquini.
This is awesome! Cute!
What? This is it.
Isn't that it?
Ah! Perf is number one!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Cute!
2,1
Last!
Miss!
Your seat!
No! No! No! No!
Don't take too many more pictures, okay?
You're so cute!
Let's get another one.
They're so cute.
Thank you.
She's cute.
Aren't you taking too many pictures? Yoo-hoo!
Hey, wait, that's really cute.
Look, look.
So cute.
Look at him.
It's a puppy.
Wow.
Cute.
Thank you.